

CONTACT

ন্ট্ৰ 27 Allée Daniel Lavallée 76000, Rouen

+33 7 66 29 08 12



bessa460@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/younesbessa



github.com/YounesBessa

younesbessa.com

LANGUAGES

Native language

Fluent (C1 level)

Conversational (B2 Level)

SKILLS

•••• HTML

••• CSS

JavaScript

React

TypeScript

Wordpress

YOUNES BESSA 23 YEARS OLD

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a 23-year-old Junior full stack Web developer from France. I study web development at Need for School in Rouen. I'm an apprentice at Expat's Facilities and I'm also part of an association called onRuntime Studio.

I like to play video games, travel and meet new people.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (2 month internship, then apprenticeship)

Expat's Facilities, Rouen | August 2021 - Present

Web Developer (two month internship)

Rouen Informatique, Rouen | April 2021 - June 2021

I designed internal digital tools related to the CRM of the company at the request of the internship supervisor and in compliance with the deadlines.

I analysed the needs and developed all the technical functionalities of these tools. I solved the problems and fixed the bugs detected by the internship supervisor.

Languages: HTML,CSS,PHP,SQL,JS Libraries: libcurl(PHP), jQuery

APIs: Google Maps API (JavaScript), Axonaut API

Framework: Bootstrap CMS: WordPress

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Web Development

Need for School, Rouen | October 2020 - Present

Programming languages and tools:

- HTML,CSS
- PHP, Symfony
- MySQL, phpMyAdmin
- JavaScript, React
- JQuery
- Wordpress

Bachelor's Degree in French Law

(First and second year)

University of Rouen, Pasteur Campus | 2018 - February 2020

Bachelor's Degree in Economic and Social Administration (First year)

University of Rouen, Pasteur Campus | 2017 - 2018

French baccalaureate (Economics branch)

French International School, Riyadh | 2017

Cambridge English Advanced Certificate, C1 level

French International High School, Jakarta | 2014